<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[jonnor]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[jonnor]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:13:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><p>In Maliit, all changes have to be reviewed by two people in order to be merged to mainline. This helps us catch issues early and keep code quality high. Since the code is hosted on Gitorious, we use their merge requests feature for that purpose. Up until now we have periodically checked the website for changes (potentially going through each and every one of the repositories), and manually mentioned updates in the IRC channel. This is both tedious and inefficient, so I wrote a simple tool to help the issue: Gitorious Merge Request Monitor</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f8005f94-5379-453b-ac5b-0dc3ef1b224c</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><h2>Current status</h2><p>MassifG is an application for visualizing the output of valgrinds massif tool. I am writing it as part of my trainee program here at Openismus. MassifG is free software, available under GPLv3. You will find the git repository at gitorious, and the tarball release for 0.1 here. Packages for Arch are available in AUR.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dbccf4e4-21dd-4330-8df0-20187778c400</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><p>As the previous post explained I was in Oslo yesterday for the Ubuntu Karmic Release party. But as I was heading for the release party I stumbled upon a friend of mine from Tønsberg. Turned out three bands from my home town were playing in Oslo that very evening, one of the bands being buddies of mine. So I got to combine two of my passions; music (metal) and free software in one evening.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ff7af24e-d60c-43e6-b916-47fcf02ff1c6</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><p>It is not well communicated, but you can apparently write your own "tabs"/"panes" for the panel/toolbar found in the Meego Netbook UX. Hopefully this blogpost helps a tiny bit*.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bfbd5d43-4507-4de5-bb63-d9d355f0b7a2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><p>While learning Qt here at Openismus I've written a basic, working plug-in for Qt that adds support for the OpenRaster file format*. Here is my Qt-based test application demoing this functionality by showing some awesome multi-layered abstract test art made by yours truly using Krita:</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">beed308e-fa83-491c-828b-26697ba7be95</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><p>Where as all my physical machines run Arch Linux, I do have some virtualized servers running Ubuntu. And in general, it is the GNU/Linux distro I recommend to people new to Linux. Not only because it has most of the things you need in a decent package and a balance between free and proprietary that I like, but also because it has a large and welcoming community. It is one of the most popular distros, and this makes it easy for people to find help when they need it. So, being the curious geek that I am, I had to check out nearest release party for Ubuntu 9.10 (Karmic Koala).</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">988ce81a-5170-447f-9008-dd23d8a0d3c3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><p>Maliit (also known as Meego Input Methods) has the following overall goal: "to be the input method project for MeeGo and other GNU/Linux-based embedded/mobile platforms".</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f6dcbcc5-5787-4c72-9e4a-097cf805bf0d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><h2>Implementation</h2><p>In learning Qt, I of course needed to get some experience with the newest and shiniest bits of Qt: Qt Quick.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d5b2405c-4472-4a60-bd79-62fbbe81256a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><p>MyPaint popularity is continuing to grow, much thanks to publicity from the Durian Open Movie project. We're now working on the v0.8 release, which hopefully will be out this year.  I wrote a small post on the official site about that here.  I'm responsible for the translations, and so far we have 11 of them, with a couple more in the works that I know of.  Packaging is also picking up, soon most of the major GNU/Linux distros will have MyPaint in the official repos! Even some talk about a Mac OSX version (using X11.app tho).</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f439d51a-a3c9-44c5-a270-2736e447927d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jon Nordby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jon Nordby</h1><p>GTK+ application support for Maliit input methods has existed for a long time, but up until now it has lived in separate repositories. This has been inconvenient for users and for developers, and was the major cause for it to not be on the same level as the Qt support. This has changed as the GTK+ support has now been merged into the maliit-framework repository, and along side the Qt support. Maliit 0.80.8, which was released yesterday, contains these changes.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/jonnor/jon-nordby/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9efa4647-bbc3-4d6e-b6c2-0ce0949b7bf7</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 18:11:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>